Finding Aid for A. Alfred Taubman College of Architecture + Urban Planning Records 1876-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Raoul G. Wallenberg
  The Raoul G. Wallenberg series holds some biographical material on Wallenberg, a 1935 graduate of the College of Architecture; files on six Wallenberg lectures, including administrative correspondence, publicity and biographies of the various speakers; general correspondence relating to Wallenberg and to the lecture as a whole; materials on the financial status of the Wallenberg Fund; publicity on Raoul Wallenberg; and a folder of miscellaneous material. One bound copy of the first lecture and an unbound copy of the second lecture have been removed and placed in the printed collection.
  A later accession of Wallenberg related material includes several photographs of Wallenberg with friends during his student days at Michigan and an image of the house he lived in while in attendance. Also included is an April 25, 1997 commemorative stamp issued by the U.S. Postal Service, a British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) produced video entitled, "Man Alive: Missing Hero," and a transcript of Senator Carl Levin's 1981 Wallenberg Lecture. Wallenberg related material is scattered throughout the record group, however, and can be found in the files of deans in addition to the Wallenberg series in this and prior accessions.
  A 2010 accession of additional Wallenberg material (1 linear foot, box 69) covers the years 1972-1997. The bulk of the records consists of files on the University's Wallenberg Lecture, though there are also several files of general correspondence, and a file on the Wallenberg scholarship fund. The lecture files are arranged chronologically and date from the 1972/73 lecture delivered by Sir Nikolaus Pevsner to the 1996/97 lecture delivered by Michael Sorkin. These files include correspondence between the lecturers and the college, articles and clipping on the lectures, and some files include transcripts of the lectures.
  - Biographical Information (Box 4)
  - Lectures
    - Arnheim, Rudolf (Box 4)
    - Bacon, Edmund (Box 4)
    - Bakema, Eric (Box 4)
    - Fitch, James Marston (Box 4)
    - Larrabee, Eric (Box 4)
    - Pevsner, Sir Nikolaus (Box 5)
  - General Correspondence (Box 5)
  - Fund (Box 5)
  - Publicity (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous/Undated (Box 5)
  - Commemorative Postage Stamp and Pin April 25, 1997 (Box 47)
  - Lecture, Carl Levin 1981 (Box 47)
  - Man Alive: Missing Hero (BBC production on Wallenberg) undated, 1 videotapes U-matic (Box 47)
  - "Memorial to Sol King, '34 in Honor of Raoul Wallenberg," 1995 (Box 47)
  - Photographs (copy) and copy negatives undated (Box 47)
    (Includes Ann Arbor house Wallenberg lived in and Wallenberg as student with friends)
  - General Correspondence 1982-1990, 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Lectures
    - 1972-1973 Sir Nikolaus Pevsner (Box 69)
    - 1973-1974 Eric Larrabee (Box 69)
    - 1974-1975 Reyner Banham (Box 69)
    - 1976-1977 Rudolf Arnheim (Box 69)
    - 1977-1978 Jacob Bakema (Box 69)
    - 1978-1979 James Marston Fitch (Box 69)
    - 1980-1981 Carl Levin (Box 69)
    - 1982-1983 Edmund Bacon (Box 69)
    - 1983-1984 Charles Correa (Box 69)
    - 1984-1985 Grady Clay (Box 69)
    - 1986-1987 Joseph Rykwert (Box 69)
    - 1987-1988 Spiro Kostof (Box 69)
    - 1988-1989 J. Max Bond (Box 69)
    - 1989-1990 Elizabeth Hollander (Box 69)
    - 1990-1991 Joseph Esherick (Box 69)
    - 1991-1992 Denise Scott Brown (Box 69)
    - 1992-1993 James Freed (Box 69)
    - 1993-1994 Jorge Silvetti (Box 69)
    - 1994-1995 Daniel Libeskind (Box 69)
    - 1995-1996 Vincent Scully (Box 69)
    - 1996-1997 Michael Sorkin (Box 69)
  - Scholarship Fund 1987-1995 (Box 69)
  - Wallenberg Medal and Lecture -- University 1986-1989 (Box 69)
    (note: different from lecture hosted by TCAUP)
- Dean's Correspondence 1969-2007
  - Robert C. Metcalf 1974-1987
    Dean's Correspondence, Robert C. Metcalf, 1974-1987 (2.3 linear feet) primarily consists of Dean Metcalf's daily correspondence from 1974 to 1987. It is chronologically arranged; most is out-going, although sometimes incoming correspondence is attached. The correspondence also includes letters written by Assistant Dean Herbert Johe and Robert M. Beckley, who was dean designate in 1986. Subjects cover the entire range of activities performed by a college dean.
    - July 1, 1974-August 31, 1974 (Box 14)
    - September 1, 1974-December 13, 1974 (Box 14)
    - January 1, 1975-February 28, 1975 (Box 14)
    - March 1, 1975-April 30, 1975 (Box 14)
    - May 1, 1975-June 27, 1975 (Box 14)
    - July 1, 1975-October 31, 1975 (Box 14)
    - November 1, 1975-December 31, 1975 (Box 14)
    - January 1 1976-February 28, 1976 (Box 14)
    - March 1, 1976-April 30, 1976 (Box 14)
    - May 1, 1976-June 30, 1976 (Box 14)
    - July 1, 1976-September 30, 1976 (Box 14)
    - October 1, 1976-November 30, 1976 (Box 14)
    - December 1, 1976-January 30, 1977 (Box 14)
    - February 1, 1977-March 31, 1977 (Box 14)
    - April 1, 1977-May 31, 1977 (Box 14)
    - June 1, 1977-July 31, 1977 (Box 14)
    - August 1, 1977-September 30, 1977 (Box 14)
    - October 1, 1977-November 30, 1977 (Box 14)
    - December 1, 1977-January 31, 1978 (Box 14)
    - February 1, 1978-March 31, 1978 (Box 14)
    - April 1, 1978-May 31, 1978 (Box 14)
    - June 1, 1978-July 31, 1978 (Box 14)
    - August 1, 1978-September 30, 1978 (Box 14)
    - October 1, 1978-November 30, 1978 (Box 14)
    - December 1, 1978-January 31, 1979 (Box 14)
    - February 1, 1979-April 30, 1979 (Box 14)
    - May 1, 1979-August 31, 1979 (Box 14)
    - September 1, 1979-November 30, 1979 (Box 15)
    - December 1, 1979-February 29, 1980 (Box 15)
    - March 1, 1980-June 30, 1980 (Box 15)
    - July 1, 1980-September 30, 1980 (Box 15)
    - October 1, 1980-January 31, 1981 (Box 15)
    - February 1, 1981-March 31, 1981 (Box 15)
    - April 1, 1981-June 30, 1981 (Box 15)
    - July 1, 1981-November 30, 1981 (Box 15)
    - December 1, 1981-March 31, 1982 (Box 15)
    - April 1, 1982-July 31, 1982 (Box 15)
    - August 1, 1982-October 31, 1982 (Box 15)
    - November 1, 1982-February 28, 1983 (Box 16)
    - March 1, 1983-June 30, 1983 (Box 16)
    - July 1, 1983-October 31, 1983 (Box 16)
    - November 1, 1983-February 29, 1984 (Box 16)
    - March 1, 1984-June 30, 1984 (Box 16)
    - July 1, 1984-October 31, 1984 (Box 16)
    - November 1, 1984-February 28, 1985 (Box 16)
    - March 1, 1985-May 31, 1985 (Box 16)
    - June 1, 1985-September 30, 1985 (Box 16)
    - October 1, 1985-January 31, 1986 (Box 16)
    - February 1, 1986-May 31, 1986 (Box 16)
    - June 1, 1986-September 30, 1986 (Box 16)
    - October 1, 1986-January 1, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Robert C. Metcalf 1969-1996
    Dean Robert Metcalf's 1969-1996 correspondence consists largely of material pertaining to his participation in professional organizations or letters of recommendation and support for students and colleagues. One expandable folder, however, holds engaging correspondence with C. Theodore Larson, a highly regarded UM professor of architecture. When Larson died in 1988, Metcalf said, "I think he was a seminal figure, one of the most innovative people we have ever had at this university...I have a whole box full of his correspondence. He was always bombarding you with ideas." (See also C. Theodore Larson papers, 1930-1985 (bulk 1951-1974), Bentley Historical Library.)
    - 1969-1996 (Box 29)
    - 1978-1991, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Larson, Theodore 1966-1985, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Robert M. Beckley 1991-1997
    Dean Robert Beckley's correspondence file is organized chronologically, January of 1991 to April of 1997. The files, broad in scope and content, testify to Beckley's meticulous and accessible management style, documenting relationships nurtured with students, faculty, alumni, and donors. His commitment to a global perspective in architectural education is also evident in the records, as is his ability to foster collegiality between visiting faculty and permanent faculty.
    - January 1991-August 1992, 13 folders (Box 30)
    - September 1992-June 1994, 21 folders (Box 31)
    - July 1994-March 1996, 21 folders (Box 32)
    - April 1996-June 1997, 15 folders (Box 33)
  - Douglas S. Kelbaugh 1999-2007
    The Kelblaugh subseries of the Dean's Correspondence series, 1999-2007 (2.5 linear feet) is comprised of Dean Douglas S. Kelbaugh's correspondence. The files in this series are organized chronologically. The first folder in the series is dated January 1999; the dates on the files then jump ahead several months and are dated from June 1999 to June 2007. Included are letters and e-mails between the dean's office, and the faculty, staff, students, and alumni of the College of Architecture and Urban Planning. There are also some letters and e-mails with other faculty and administrators at the University of Michigan, as well as correspondence with faculty and administrators from other universities. Although there are some printed e-mails included in the collection, a more complete record of Dean Kelbaugh's e-mail correspondence may be found digitally.
    - January 1999 (Box 60)
    - June 1999-May 2002, 36 folders (Box 60)
    - June 2002-December 2004, 31 folders (Box 61)
    - January 2005-June 2007, 30 folders (Box 62)
  - Snyder, James C., Interim Dean 1997-1998
    The Dean's Correspondence, 1997-1998 (0.25 linear ft.), is comprised of several folders of correspondence generated from the office of James Snyder while he served as interim dean of the college.
    - 1997-1998, 9 folders (Box 51)
- Doctoral Program Files 1969-1997
  The Doctoral Program Files (1 linear foot) are arranged in topical order and cover the period 1969-1987. These files consist of program evaluations, student profiles, dissertation lists and program requirements. Of particular interest are the files of the "Doctoral Program Committee." These annual files include lists of students, their field of study and advisor, dissertation proposal/abstracts, some committee minutes, and seminar class information. Program requirements, goals, and objectives can be ascertained from the many evaluative reports found under the heading "Reports." In addition, the "Doctoral Program Council" folder also contains evaluative program materials. The researcher will also find goals and objectives, sources of student financial aid, and a proposal for the Doctor of Architecture program within the "Historical Materials" folder.
  - Annual Report File 1981-1984 (Box 19)
  - Dissertation List 1971-1986 (Box 19)
  - Doctoral Program Committee
    - 1969-1971 (Box 19)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 19)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 19)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 19)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 19)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 19)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 19)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 19)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 19)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 19)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 19)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 19)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Doctoral Program Council 1978-1985 (review of doctoral program) (Box 19)
  - Historical Materials 1967-1984 (Box 19)
  - Rackham Review Committee 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Reports
    - Faculty Evaluation of the Doctoral Program (authored by Ben Handler), 1986 (Box 20)
    - Report to the Department of Architecture, 1972 (Box 20)
      (evaluation of doctoral program authored by D.H. Carson)
    - Report of the Committee to Evaluate the Doctoral Program in Urban and Regional Planning at the University of Michigan, 1979 (Box 20)
    - Report of the Ph.D. Review Committee for the College of Architecture and Urban Planning circa 1978 (Box 20)
  - Student/Faculty Listing 1982-1984 (Box 20)
  - Student Funding 1972-1985 (Box 20)
  - Urban & Regional Planning Program Committee 1979-1981 (Box 20)
- Topical Files 1926-2004
  The Topical Files consist of two chronologically overlapping alphabetically arrange files. Though each contains some material dating back as far as 1926, the bulk of the files are from the 1970-1990.
  - 1926-1993, 1975-1990
    The Topical Files, 1926-1993 enhance this record group's documentation of student activities. A several year span of entries for the George Booth Traveling Fellowship in Architecture includes many imaginative proposals by young alumni. The researcher will also find submissions for the first Saarinen-Swanson Essay Contest, held in 1989. Also included are the bylaws of the student chapter of American Institute of Architects (AIA), and information about visiting scholars and lecturers.
    The faculty records represented include materials collected for promotion review, and the confidential papers surrounding the promotion committee decision process. Although the latter records are restricted, the former are open to research.
    There are some administrative files as well, covering topics such as affirmative action, availability assessments and the raw data collected for the National Architectural Accrediting Board (NAAB) annual surveys. There are also some records for the Art and Architecture and Slide Libraries.
    - Affirmative Action (Box 23)
      - Correspondence 1969-1987, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Statistics 1987-1989 (Box 23)
    - Alumni Luncheon at Annual AIA Convention 1966-1988, 5 folders (Box 23)
    - Appeals Procedure 1969-1974 (Box 22)
    - Architectural Research Lab 1967-1973 (Box 23)
    - Art and Architecture Building
      - Articles 1971-1972 (Box 23)
      - Dedication Ceremony 1975 (Box 23)
      - Groundbreaking Ceremony 1972 (Box 23)
      - Naming of Building 1974 (Box 23)
    - Art and Architecture Library
      - Library Committee 1955, 1977-1981 (Box 23)
      - Slide Library
        - Cataloging Guidelines 1981-1990, undated (Box 23)
        - Correspondence 1986-1993, 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Symposium on the Architecture Library of the Future 1987 (Box 23)
    - Availability Assessment Surveys
      - 1973 (Box 23)
      - 1976 (Box 23)
      - 1978 (Box 23)
      - 1979 (Box 23)
    - Booth, George G. Traveling Fellowship in Architecture
      - General Information 1989-1991 (Box 23)
      - Proposals 1990-1995, 11 folders (Box 23)
    - Budget Issues 1974-1981 (Box 23)
    - "Central" Publication of the Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture, East Central Region 1978-1986 (Box 24)
    - CAUP Retreat 1988 (Box 24)
    - College Rules and Regulations 1955-1988 (Box 24)
    - Computer Facilities 1966-1988, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Demonstration Unit for Environmental Technologies (DUET) 1968-1972 (Box 24)
    - Doctoral Program in Architecture, Dissertation Abstracts 1971-1987 (Box 24)
    - Domino's Pizza Top 30 Architects 1988 (Box 24)
    - Exhibits
      - Connections 1988-1990 (Box 24)
      - Possibilities 1987-1990 (Box 24)
    - Faculty News Items 1977-1987 (Box 24)
    - Faculty Salary Scale 1969-1986, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Fuller, R. Buckminster and Dymaxion Dome Project 1954 (Box 24)
      (see also Photographs)
    - Graduate Recognition Ceremony and Open House 1977-1986 (Box 24)
    - Havemeyer Collection of the College of Architecture and Design 1971-1982 (Box 24)
    - Hires, Joint Appointment Attempt 1992-1993 (Box 22)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2023 ]
    - Lectures
      - Budgets 1986-1991 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence with Visiting Lecturers 1987-1991, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Publicity 1986-1989 (Box 24)
      - Series Schedules 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Lorch, Emil. Letter to Dean Youtz 1960 (Box 24)
    - King, Martin Luther. MLK Day Program 1992 (Box 24)
    - Name for Old Architecture Building 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - National Architectural Accrediting Board (NAAB)
      - Raw Data Collected for the Survey 1975-1986, 10 folders (Box 24)
      - Reports for the NAAB
        - 1986, 1993, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Visiting Team Report 1989 (Box 24)
    - Promotions
      - Materials Presented to Review Committee
        - 1956 (Box 25)
        - 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 25)
        - 1977-1992, 9 folders (Box 22)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2022 ]
    - Reappointments
      - 1986-1988, 8 folders (Box 22)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2018 ]
    - Reports
      - "The Approach, Subject-Matter and Curriculum of Planning" by the Committee on the Planning Committee 1958 (Box 25)
      - Architecture Program Chair 1988 (Box 25)
      - Building Safety Survey 1966 (Box 25)
      - Dean's Self-Study and Plan for the Future 1985 (Box 25)
      - Proposal for Revisions to the Doctoral Program in Architecture, including background material 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Proposed Doctor of Architecture Program 1968-1969 (Box 25)
      - Strategic Planning Report 1988 (Box 25)
      - Urban, Technological, and Environmental Planning, an Interdisciplinary Ph.D. Program 1985 (Box 25)
    - Saarinen-Swanson Essay Competition 1989, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Searches
      - Associate Dean 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 22)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2017 ]
      - Doctoral Program in Architecture Chair 1988-1989 (Box 22)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2019 ]
    - University of Michigan Student Chapter of AIA
      - Bylaws 1940, 1956, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Sixth Annual Student Forum 1960 (Box 25)
    - Visiting Scholars 1980-1987, 5 folders (Box 25)
    - Welding Unit 1969-1971 (Box 25)
  - 1926-1991, circa 1970-1990
    The Topical Files, 1926-1991 (2.5 linear ft.) is comprised of material from a variety of sources. The nearly one foot of brochures representing a range of mainly Michigan architects, for example, was once a part of the Art and Architecture Library. Also generated from the library are photocopies of 1922-1923 correspondence between Emil Lorch and Frank Lloyd Wright, and photocopies of Eliel Saarinen related clippings and correspondence. In addition, the series brings together various papers and reports, including Emil Lorch's "Collections of the College, 1906-1936," a 1949 Mid-Century Report on Design Progress, and a 1988 strategic planning report. The series also holds further documentation of the Norman Committee in the form of correspondence, minutes, and membership lists. Other files include a medallion celebrating the 1972 groundbreaking for the North Campus building; commencement programs, 1980-1999; and a 1929 letter sent to President Ruthven by several alumni urging the separation of the College of Architecture from the College of Engineering.
    - ACSA Teacher's Seminar at Cranbrook circa 1979, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Alumni 1988-1992 (Box 45)
    - Alumni Letter to President Ruthven 1929 (Box 45)
    - Architectural Firm Brochures circa 1960s-1980s
      - A.W. Kutsche & Co. (Box 45)
      - Albert Kahn Associates (Box 45)
      - Ayres, Lewis, Norris & Mary (Box 45)
      - Begrow & Brown (Box 45)
      - Calvin Robinson Associates (Box 45)
      - Crane & Gorwic (Box 45)
      - Dauerman Associates (Box 45)
      - DeVries Associates (Box 45)
      - Eberle M. Smith Associates (Box 45)
      - Gerald Crane & Norbet Gorwic (Box 45)
      - Glen Paulsen & Associates (Box 45)
      - Harley, Ellington, Cowin and Stirton, 4 items (Box 45)
      - Hobbs & Black Associates (Box 45)
      - Jahr-Anderson-Machida Associates (Box 45)
      - Kingscott Associates, 2 items (Box 45)
      - O'Dell Hewlett & Luckenbach Associates (Box 45)
      - Robert Lee Wald & Associates (Box 45)
      - Smith, Hinchman & Grylls Associates (Box 45)
      - Smith, Smith Haynes Lundberg & Waehler (Box 45)
      - Stickel & Moody & Associates, 2 items (Box 45)
      - Suren Pilafian (Box 45)
      - Swanson Associates (Box 45)
      - Tarapata MacMahon Associates (Box 45)
      - Warren Holmes & Kenneth Black (Box 45)
      - William Kessler and Associates (Box 45)
    - Commencement (Box 46)
      - 1987 (mainly photographs) (Box 46)
      - 1988 (Box 46)
      - 1991 (Box 46)
    - Design for Aging Course Material 1982 (Box 46)
    - Educational Program Committee 1966 (Box 46)
    - Medallion, Groundbreaking, Art & Architecture Building 1972 (Box 46)
    - Norman Committee 1974 (Report, minutes, membership, correspondence, etc. of Review Committee), 1 folders (Box 46)
      (see also Box 8)
    - Papers, Articles, Reports
      - General 1959-1982 (Box 46)
      - "Basic Human Needs and the Housing Environment," 1975 (Box 46)
      - "Collections of the College, 1906-1936," Emil Lorch (Box 46)
      - "Central Campus Redevelopment," Philip B. Wargelin and John D. Telfer 1960 (Box 46)
      - Design Fundamentals, undated (Box 46)
      - Design and the Urban Core: Creating a Relevant Milieu, James Alvin Chaffers, 1971 (Box 46)
      - Leonard B. Willeke Design Prize, Report of the Competition Committee, 1986 (Box 46)
      - Mid-Century Report on Design Progress Review-Preview, 1949 (Box 46)
      - "Report to the Faculty of the College of Architecture and Design," Reginald F. Malcolmson, Dean," 1965 (Box 46)
      - "Research Activities," 1956 (Box 46)
      - Review of the Program, Masters in Urban Planning, 1979 (Box 46)
      - Strategic Planning Report, 1988 (Box 46)
      - "Tiffany Glass," Patricia Siemon 1971 (Box 46)
      - Utilization of Space Report, 1965 (Box 46)
    - Planning and Space
      - Energy, Art and Architecture Building undated (Box 46)
      - Architecture Building, Report On 1966, 1968 (Box 46)
      - Library for the Art and Architecture Building, Art 383 1980 (Box 46)
      - Program Analysis and Design Criteria Analysis 1969 (Box 46)
      - Specifications for the Architectural Building, University of Michigan, Emil Lorch and Associates, Architects, 1926 (Box 46)
      - Ten Arquitectos
        (see also drawings in Drawer 1)
        - Project Proposal 1999 (Box 46)
        - Art & Architecture Building Program for Regeneration 1999 (Box 46)
    - Resume Book 1996, 1998 (Box 47)
    - Resume Guidelines 1994 (Box 47)
    - Saarinen, Eliel 1923-1924 (Box 47)
      (photocopies of correspondence, clippings, etc)
    - Scholars and Patrons Supper 1987-1996 (Box 47)
    - Semi-Centennial Celebration 1956 (Box 47)
    - Testimonials (Detroit General Council and General Services Administration (GSA)) 1978-1979 (Box 47)
    - Unistrut 1954-1956 (Box 47)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd 1922-1923 (Box 47)
      (mainly photocopies of correspondence with Emil Lorch)
  - 1967-2004
    The Topical Files 1967-2004 subseries,(3 linear feet) contains materials on other activities and events involving the College of Architecture and Urban Planning, and are split into General Files, 1967-2003 and Lectures, 1979-2004. Included in the General Files are materials on the Architecture and Planning Research Laboratory (APRL), the Faculty Development Fund, and the Willeke Design Competition. There are also articles and letters regarding the trial of A. Alfred Taubman in 2003. The Lectures files include several files of correspondence with visiting lecturers, as well as files on the Dinkeloo Memorial Lecture, and the lecture series schedules for the years 1988-1993, 1999-2001, and 2003-2004.
    - General Files 1967-2000
      - Alpha Rho Chi Lecture Program -- "Connections -- Uses of the Past" March 1978 (delivered by Charles W. Moore) (Box 70)
      - Architecture and Planning Research Laboratory (APRL)
        - General, no date (Box 70)
        - Building Technology Laboratory (BTL) 1987 (Box 70)
        - Daylight Simulator 1987 (Box 70)
        - Design America 1987-1988 (Box 70)
      - Cass Corridor Design Studio 1999 (Box 70)
      - Detroit Housing Prototype Design Studio 1999-2000 (proposal submitted to Arts of Citizenship (Aoc) program; this project developed from team work during the first annual Detroit Design Charrette) (Box 70)
      - Emeritus Reunion Weekend
        - 1999 (Box 70)
        - 2000 (Box 70)
        - 2001 (Box 70)
        - 2002 (Box 70)
      - Exhibits
        - Bailey, Roger 1981-1982 (Box 70)